

- **L** +58 4241945619
- dianagsisiruca@gmail.com
- ♥ Caracas Venezuela.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering University Alejandro de Humboldt. Caracas - Venezuela

2020 - 2023

LANGUAGE

- Spanish (Native)
- English (C1)
- Portuguese (B2)
- Chinese (A1)

SKILLS

- Strong leadership and organizational skills developed through coordinating English programs.
- Proficiency in Microsoft Office, Google Drive, and Windows SQL server.
- Basic knowledge of programming languages.
- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.
- Problem-solving abilities.

DIANA CRISTINA GOMES SISIRUCA

Computer Engineer

ABOUT ME

I am a 24-year-old recent graduate in Computer Engineering seeking a challenging opportunity to further develop my skills in the field of IT. I am particularly interested in a position that allows me to contribute to projects related to web development and computer systems while continuously learning and growing within the company.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

O Sept 2016 - Present Funesl Academy C.A

English Coordinator

- Coordinated English language programs, including curriculum development and assessment.
- Provided leadership and mentorship to a team of instructors, fostering a positive learning environment.
- Collaborated with the IT department to oversee the construction of the company's website.
- Managed computer technical support services, troubleshooting and resolving hardware and software issues.

Jun 2023 - Present Calliope Interactive

Supervisor of Communications and Interactive Reading Platform, Website and App Management

- Email Reading and Organization
- Efficiently read and organize incoming emails to ensure timely responses and prioritize tasks.
- CV Review for Authors and Illustrators
- Thoroughly review CVs of authors and illustrators, ensuring alignment with the company's profile and requirements.
- Book Reading and Classification
- Read and classify books to determine their suitability for publication on an interactive reading platform.
- App and Website Supervision
- Supervise the company's app and website to ensure smooth functionality and an optimal user experience.



- +58 4241945619
- dianagsisiruca@gmail.com
- Caracas Venezuela.

EDUCACIÓN

Ingeniería Informática

Universidad Alejandro de Humboldt, Caracas - Venezuela 2020 - 2023

IDIOMAS

- Español (Native)
- Inglés (C1)
- Portugues (B2)
- Chino Mandarín (A1)

HABILIDADES

- Liderazgo y destrezas desarrolladas a través de la coordinación de programas de inglés.
- Proficiencia en Microsoft Office, Google Drive y Windows SQL Server.
- Conocimientos básicos de lenguajes de programación.
- Excelentes habilidades de comunicación e interpersonales y trabajo en equipo.
- Habilidades para la resolución de problemas.

DIANA CRISTINA GOMES SISIRUCA

Ingeniera Informática

SOBRE MÍ

Tengo 24 años recién graduada en Ingeniería Informática en busca de una oportunidad desafiante para desarrollar aún más mis habilidades en el campo de Tecnología de la Información. Estoy particularmente interesada en un puesto que me permita contribuir a proyectos relacionados con el desarrollo web y sistemas informáticos, mientras sigo aprendiendo y creciendo dentro de la empresa.

EXPERIENCIA PROFESIONAL

o Sept 2016 - Presente Funesl Academy C.A

Coordinadora de Inglés

- Coordinar programas de inglés, considerando la planificación, desarrollo de currículo y evaluación.
- Proporcionar liderazgo y mentoría a facilitadores o instructores, fomentando un ambiente de aprendizaje positivo y trabajo en equipo.
- Planificar y desarrollar la construcción del sitio web de la empresa.
- Gestionar el servicio de soporte técnico de computadoras, solucionando problemas de hardware y software.

O Jun 2023 - Presente Calliope Interactive

Supervisora de Comunicaciones y Plataforma de Lectura Interactiva, Gestión del Sitio Web y Aplicación.

- Leer y organizar eficientemente los correos electrónicos entrantes para garantizar respuestas oportunas y priorizar tareas o requerimientos.
- Examinar minuciosamente los CV de autores e ilustradores, asegurando que estén en línea con el perfil y requisitos de la empresa.
- Leer y clasificar libros para determinar su idoneidad para su publicación en una plataforma de lectura interactiva.
- Supervisar la aplicación y el sitio web de la empresa, para garantizar un funcionamiento óptimo y una experiencia satisfactoria del usuario.